DEPORT ALL GODS.
Black Site is a action, horror, science fiction film directed by Tom Paton.
80's inspired John Carpenteresque Action.
A young woman is forced to push past her worst fears and battle to
deport an ancient entity back to where it came from.
Set inside an underground military base known as The Artemis Black Site, the movie mixes an Escape From New
York style survival story with Lovecraftian elements and large scale mythology building.
Agent Ackerman, played by Jessica-Jane Stafford.
Sam, played by Mike Beckingham.
Agent Leonhart, played by Lauren Ashley Carter.
Danforth, played by Sophia Del Pizzo.
Cult of Erebus, played by Luke D'Silva.
Jay Austin, played by Bentley Kalu.
Black Site is a 2018 British science-fiction action horror film directed by Tom Paton, starring Samantha Schnitzler, Mike Beckingham, Kris Johnson,
Bentley Kalu, Angela Dixon, Phoebe Robinson-Rodrigues, Sophia Del Pizzo, Andy Gibbins, Jessica-Jane Clement, Fredi Nwaka and Alana Wallace.
The film explores themes of mythology, military base, creature, entity, ancient.
The tone is dark and thought_provoking.